A Guide to the Papers of the Charlottesville-Albemarle Association for the Fine Arts 1982-1997
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
{Special Collections, University of Virginia Library}
Papers of the Charlottesville-Albemarle Association for the Fine Arts 1982-1997
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11460
ca. 500 items (2 Hollinger boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift: Jan Daggett, Charlottesville, Va., January 15, 1999.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of the papers of the Charlottesville-Albemarle Association for the Fine Arts, an affiliate of the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1982-1997, ca. 500 items (2 Hollinger boxes). The records include corporate records, financial and bank statements, legal papers concerning the tax-exempt status of the organization, insurance papers, annual reports of the Virginia State Corporation Commission, membership and mailing lists, correspondence with the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, by-laws, minutes of meetings, papers about films, workshops, publicity, safaris, and the dissolution of the chapter.
Contents List
- Annual Reports of the Virginia State Corporation Commission 1991, 1995-1997 (Box 1)
- Application for Recognition of Tax Exemption 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Bank Statements 1996-1997 (Box 1)
- Bulk Mailing 1986-1997 (Box 1)
- By-laws 1989 (Box 1)
- Change of Address 1997 (Box 1)
- Community Workshops 1984-1991 (Box 1)
- Corporate Records 1989 (Box 1)
- Correspondence with the Virginia Museum of Fine Arts 1989-1997 (Box 1)
- Expenses 1996-1997 (Box 1)
- Films 1990-1991 (Box 1)
- Financial Statements 1988-1997 (Box 1)
- Insurance 1990, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
- Kappa Sigma Fraternity 1990-1992 (Box 2)
- Minutes of Board Meetings 1990-1992 (Box 2)
- Minutes of Meetings 1986-1991, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Programs 1987-1997 (Box 2)
- Publicity 1984-1990 (Box 2)
- Safaris 1982-1993 (Box 2)
- Tax-Exempt Status 1986-1995 (Box 2)